networkencyclopedia.com 2019-12-16

# Privacy Policy – Network Encyclopedia

We respect our users’ privacy. This page describes our privacy policy and you should read it to learn more about us.

## Who we are

This website is the property of CIBERFORMA LDA

Our website address is: https://networkencyclopedia.com.

For more information visit our contact page.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

## Who we share your data with

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## General Privacy Policy from Ciberforma Websites

By coming to a CIBERFORMA website, you are agreeing to and accepting this Privacy Policy as well as the terms and conditions or other end-user agreement for that site.

  * We will not distribute information that identifies you individually or reveals your identity (“Identifying Information”) unless you give your prior approval in response to a request made by CIBERFORMA or unless distribution of this information is permitted under this Privacy Policy. Your electronic approval will qualify as your consent for this purpose.
  * We will not make Identifying Information available publicly without the prior written or electronic consent of the individual identified unless (a) the information is already publicly available; (b) required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority; or (c) the information is posted by the user to an on-line bulletin board, chat room, newsgroups, or another public forum.
  * We may collect and use information about you and your use of the CIBERFORMA sites, including Identifying Information, for our own internal purposes such as, for example, analyzing usage of the CIBERFORMA sites in order to improve them.
  * We may use and/or distribute information about you and your use of the CIBERFORMA sites in forms that do not identify you individually or reveal your identity.
  * Advertisements, promotional offers, promotional emails, “free gifts,” and links, for example, on the CIBERFORMA sites or sent via email or other means from CIBERFORMA may ask for Identifying Information from you. If you provide this information, your Identifying Information may be provided (either directly from you or by CIBERFORMA) to the advertiser or web site or company making the offer or providing the gift. You may opt-out regarding how Identifying Information collected from you may be used or distributed when provided to CIBERFORMA at a CIBERFORMA site by either following the applicable instructions and links on the site, in the email or other documents, or by sending an email to the CIBERFORMA site Web Master at thenetwo@thenetworkencyclopedia.com or as otherwise posted on the CIBERFORMA sites. To ensure that your opt-out email is effective, you must include the words “opt-out” and “Identifying Information” in the subject field of such email.
  * CIBERFORMA may send users, via email or other means, information relating to CIBERFORMA sites and/or information on specials, new products and/or promotions from our marketing partners/colleagues. The information described in these messages is intended to be of high interest or value to our users. To choose not to receive such messages, a user can simply click or go to a URL link located in every email or other message containing this kind of information, which will remove the user from future mailings. Or, for certain sites, a user may edit his/her personal account information, which contains an option on receiving special offers, at any time by clicking the appropriate link on the applicable CIBERFORMA site.
  * In the course of our business, CIBERFORMA might buy or sell sites or assets. In these kinds of transactions, customer information (such as Identifying Information) is usually one of the transferred business assets. In the event that CIBERFORMA, its parent, subsidiaries, or affiliates is acquired, merged, or otherwise combined with another party, customer information (such as Identifying Information) will be one of the transferred assets.
  * CIBERFORMA may use other companies and persons to perform certain functions for us. These functions might include, for example, processing credit card payments, providing customer service, and sending an email. These other companies and persons may have access to customer information (such as Identifying Information) that are needed to perform their functions, but they are not authorized to use it for any other purposes. In addition, we may share information with other affiliated companies and joint ventures, for example, but we obligate those companies to honor the standards of this Privacy Policy.

In order to provide our users with a more complete understanding of how the CIBERFORMA sites collect and use information from our users, we have provided the following information: Internet Protocol (IP) Address.  
The CIBERFORMA sites log IP addresses for systems administration, diagnostic, and site tracking purposes, and to report aggregate information to advertisers. The CIBERFORMA sites do not link IP addresses to information identifying users individually.  
Cookies  
The CIBERFORMA sites may use files called “cookies” to store usernames, passwords, and other user preferences so that users don’t have to re-enter this information each time they use a particular CIBERFORMA site. You should be aware that advertisers serving ads on the CIBERFORMA sites may use their own cookies.

###   
Information Collection and Opt-Out

The CIBERFORMA sites registration forms ask users to enter contact information (like their email address), general information (like their city, state), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The forms also require unique identifiers (username and password) so that users can be verified when they access the CIBERFORMA sites. The contact information primarily is used to send users daily emails and other information they have requested and other information as stated in this Privacy Policy. Users may opt-out of receiving future email updates by clicking on or going to the applicable link in any email or other document and following the instructions. The demographic information is used among other things, to tailor users’ experiences at the CIBERFORMA sites, distribute and show you content that we think you might be interested in, and display site content according to your preferences. 

In addition, advertisers or web sites that have links on the CIBERFORMA sites may collect personally identifiable information about you. The privacy and information practices of those advertisers or web sites linked to the CIBERFORMA sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

Changes to this Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is subject to modification from time to time.   
If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact:  
geral[at]ciberforma.pt

_Updated: March 18, 2018_
